That it looks like we ran into this error, no such file or directory,
啊，看来我们遇到了报错，“没有这样的文件或目录”
it looks like our code might not have compiled correctly here.
看起来我们的代码可能没有正确编译
So here's what I'm gonna do.
这里我打算这么做
We're gonna go ahead and delete our artifacts to trash.
我要删除我们的 "artifacts"，移动到回收站
We're gonna delete our cache as well.
同时也删除我们的 "cache"
And we're going to try rerunning this
接着我会尝试重新运行一下这个
whenever you run a script with the hard drive command Hardhead will automatically recompile it for you,
每当你使用 Hardhat 命令运行脚本时，Hardhat 都会自动为你重新编译一次
especially if there's no artifacts folder.
尤其是没有 "artifacts" 文件夹的时候
So we're going to rerun this command and heartbeat, it's going to compile first
所以我们要重新运行一下这个命令，并且 Hardhat 会首先进行编译
and we can see that it does exactly that.
可以看到它确实是这样的
And then it's going to go ahead and redeploy.
接着它就会继续重新部署
Hopefully this time, it should be able to find the contract that had just compiled
希望这一次，它能找到刚刚编译好的合约
looks like this time after I deleted the artifacts folder,
看来这一次，在我删掉 "artifacts" 文件夹后
we actually did indeed get some successful compilation.
我们确实成功完成了编译
And we can see here successfully submitted source code for contract
并且我们可以看到，“成功提交了合约的源代码”
or verification on the block explore waiting for verification results,
于区块浏览器上进行验证，正在等待验证结果
successfully verified contracts simple storage on ether scan,
成功在 etherscan 上验证了 SimpleStorage 合约
and even gives us a link that we can go ahead and Command click or control click into.
它甚至还给了我们一个链接，使用 "Command" 点击或 "Ctrl" 点击以进入
And we can see the contract indeed being verified.
并且我们可以看到合约确实已经被验证了
This is awesome.
真是太棒了